A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Audiovisual materials, Series 39 FA756
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Audiovisual materials, Series 39
1945-1976
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
Danzig, Jerry A.
FA756
14.5 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
Audiovisual material (motion picture film, video, and audio recordings) pertaining to NAR's gubernatorial and political career.
Arrangement
Arranged in subseries by media type (film, video) and chronologically by creation date.
Sound recordings; Moving Images
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, Political Films, 1945-1976; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Footage from campaigns, conventions, and official events that are specifically related to political activities in the life of NAR. Many dozens of campaign commercials, including TV and radio spots.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  All inquiries to view films require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
  Arrangement
  Chronological.
  - Undated
    - WNBF-TV Interview with NAR, pre 1958; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1258)
      Scope and Contents note
      Interview with Nelson Rockefeller about George Hindman and the State Constitutional Commission (filmed pre-1958).
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Homenaje a los Alcaldes de Puerto Rico, Sound, Color, 8 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1116)
      produced by the Miller Brewing Company, footage of awards dinner with Governor Nelson Rockefeller and other speakers, featuring Miller High Life beers as sponsor. Also has footage of the Puerto Rico Day Parade in Manhattan.
  - 1945
    - United Nations Conference with U.S. Delegates, 1945; Sound, Black and white, 9 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1656)
      Nelson Rockefeller is shown at beginning of international conference.
      Open for research. Digital access copy available.
    - Pan-American Day, 1945 April 14; Sound, Black and white, 12 minutes; 35mm film (Reel AV 1618)
      Presentation of a proclamation from Connecticut Governor Raymond B. Baldwin to Secretary of State Nelson Rockefeller.
  - 1958
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller: Newsreel Compilation from Fox News, 1958; Sound, Black and white, 11 minutes; 35mm film (Reel AV 1700)
      A newsreel compilation from 1958 of Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial footage. Includes footage of Nelson A. Rockefeller in New York City at a reception for his gubernatorial campaign, Dwight D. Eisenhower arriving in New York City, Nelson A. Rockefeller and Dwight D. Eisenhower in 5th Avenue parade, John D. Rockefeller 3rd with Senator Keating, construction of the Interfaith Center, Nelson A. Rockefeller family portrait, President Eisenhower with Nelson Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller and David Kennedy, Nelson A. Rockefeller campaiging in Glen Falls, New York. Nelson A. Rockefeller and wife visiting Venezuela. Nelson A. Rockefeller in Albany, New York at swearing in ceremony and celeration. Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller and Nelson sewing union labels on clothing.
    - Dewey Endorsement of Republican Candidates, 1958; Silent, Black and white, 16 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1544)
      1958 campaign, Thomas Dewey's endorsements of candidates Nelson Rockefeller, Wilson, Keating, and Lefkowitz, shot by CBS.
    - Kenneth Keating, 1958; Sound, Black and white, 14 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1558)
      1958 Campaign: footage of President Eisenhower and Senator Javits visiting with candidate Keating.
    - Rockefeller on the Issues: Speaking From the Desk, 1958; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1543)
      Episode 12 of a series of broadcast speeches during the 1958 campaign, produced by the New York StateYS Republican Committee.
    - NAR Appearance on "Face the Nation", 1958 January 12; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1073)
    - NAR on the Issues of Organized Labor, 1958 October 20; Sound, Black and white, 14 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1530)
      Remarks of Governor Rockefeller from the New York Republican state Committee Meeting
    - Senator Jacob Javits Speech, 1958 October 20; Sound, Black and white, 15 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1559)
      Senator Jacob Javits speech on behalf of NAR gubernatorial campaign
    - Five Candidates: Rockefeller on the Issues, 1958 (Reel AV 1659)
      1958 show with Rockefeller, Keating, Wilson, Lefkowitz and Lundy.
    - Keating Interview, 1958 (Reel AV 1655)
  - 1959
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller on Meet the Press, 1959 July 19.; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1082)
      Interviews with Governor Rockefeller.
    - Paul Coates Show Interview with Governor Rockefeller, 1959 December 1; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1083)
  - 1960
    - Governor Rockefeller Reports: Budget, 1960; Sound, Black and white, 15 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1678)
      A discussion with Senator Austin Erwin, finance commissioner, from a series of broadcast reports filmed by CBS.
    - NAR on Face the Nation, 1960 July 3; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1079)
    - Making of the President, Sound, Black and white, 90 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1148)
      Based on the book by Theodore H. White, this documentary film follows the campaigns of Nixon and John F. Kennedy during the 1960 presidential election, with news footage of Nelson Rockefeller, Hubert Humphreys, and others. Produced by David Wolper for ABC-TV news.
    - 1960 National Campaign: "Leadership", "Economic Growth", "Equal Opportunity", "Foreign Policy", Sound, Black and white, 1-4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1184)
      Titles include E-20-15 LEADERSHIP; E-20-16 ECONOMIC GROWTH; E-20-17 EQUAL OPPORTUNITY; E-20-18 FOREIGN POLICY.
      Related Materials
      ALSO SEE III 14.1 Fa 81 (AV 1232); COMPILED ON ONE REEL WITH AV #1232-1234.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Endorses Richard Nixon in His Campaign for Presidency, 1960; 16mm film (negative) (Reel AV 1542A, Reel AV 1542B)
      Governor Rockefeller and President Eisenhower endorse Nixon as the Republican presidential candidate.
    - National Campaign: Eisenhower for Nixon, 1960; Sound, Black and white, 4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1234)
      Footage from Channel E-24 of the New York Republican State Committee, during the 1960 presidential election.
    - National Campaign: GOP National Convention, 1960; Sound, Black and white, 11 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1146)
      Footage of Barry M. Goldwater's speech at the 1960 GOP Convention, withdrawing his candidacy in support of Richard Nixon. Goldwater speaks about the history and purpose of the Republican party, and asks for unity within the party.
    - National Campaign: Nelson A. Rockefeller on the Kennedy Record, 1960; Sound, Black and white, 4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1233)
      Footage from Channel E-24 from the 1960 presidential election
    - 1960 National Campaign: "Civil Rights", "Economic Growth", "Disarmament", "Leadership", Sound, Black and white, 4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1232)
      E-60-11; E-60-12, E-60-13; E-60-14
  - 1961
    - Governor Rockefeller Reports: Proposals to the Legislature, 1961 January 1; Sound, Black and white, 15 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1683)
      One episode from a series of broadcast reports, filmed by CBS-TV.
  - 1962
    - Pre-Convention Campaign Commercials., 1962; Sound/Silent, Black and white, varying durations, usually about 1 minute
      Contains about 40 commercials from NAR's 1962 Gubernatorial campaign. Some duplicates or revised versions included.
      When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
      - Aid to Labor, 1962; 16mm film (Reel AV 1176)
      - Aid to New York City, 1962 (Reel AV 1225, Reel AV 1224)
      - Atomic Research, 1962 (Reel AV 1177)
      - Civil Rights and the Aged, 1962 (Reel AV 1183)
        File Plan
        III 14.1 Fa 29
      - College, 1962 (Reel AV 1162)
        III 14.1 Fa 8
      - College Education, 1962 (Reel AV 1167, Reel AV 1158, Reel AV 1169)
      - Conservation and Recreation, 1962 (Reel AV 1178)
      - Education, 1962 (Reel AV 1174)
      - Fiscal Integrity, 1962 (Reel AV 1175)
      - Higher Education, 1962 (Reel AV 1180)
      - Highway Construction, 1962 (Reel AV 1179)
      - Housing, 1962 (Reel AV 1168)
        III 14.1 Fa 14
      - Housing and Urban Renewal, 1962 (Reel AV 1181)
      - Human Rights, 1962 (Reel AV 1160)
      - Jobs, 1962 (Reel AV 1165, Reel AV 1154)
      - Jobs and Economic Growth, 1962 (Reel AV 1230)
      - Law and Narcotics, 1962 (Reel AV 1182)
      - Money, 1962 (Reel AV 1166)
      - NAR: Albany, 1962 (Reel AV 1171)
      - NAR: Buffalo, 1962 (Reel AV 1172)
      - NAR: New York City, 1962 (Reel AV 1173)
      - Narcotics, 1962 (Reel AV 1231)
      - New Yorker, 1962 (Reel AV 1164)
      - Record, 1962 (Reel AV 1226)
      - Record, New York City, 1962 (Reel AV 1159, Reel AV 1222, Reel AV 1227)
      - Record, Upstate, 1962 (Reel AV 1228, Reel AV 1223)
      - School Aid, 1962 (Reel AV 1170, Reel AV 1161, Reel AV 1157)
      - Senior Citizens, 1962 (Reel AV 1156)
      - Women, 1962 (Reel AV 1163)
      - Housing, 1962 (Reel AV 1229)
        Sound, Black and white, 5 minutes. Only available on 16mm.
        III 14.1 Fa 78
    - 1962 Address to the New York State Legislature, 1962 January 1; Sound, Black and white, 60 minutes (Reel AV 1716, Reel AV 1717)
      CBS-TV coverage of state address by Governor Rockefeller.
    - NAR on At The Source, 1962 January; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1084)
    - NAR on Newsmakers, 1962 October 21; Sound, Black and white, 28 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1094)
    - Pure Water Bonds Proposition 1 Commercials, 1963; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute (each); 16mm film (Reel AV 1204, Reel AV 1205, Reel AV 1207, Reel AV 1206)
      Several public service announcements that ran on TV in 1963 in support of Pure Bond issues.
    - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller Swearing-In: Official Highlights, 1962 December 31; Silent, Black and white, 3 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1545)
      Govenor Nelson A. Rockefeller swearing-in ceremony at executive mansion in Albany, New York: Official highlights.
  - 1963
    - Governor Rockefeller Inauguration, 1963 January 1; Sound and silent. Black and white, 18 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1666)
    - NAR on Newsmakers, 1963 February 23; Sound, Black and white, 28 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1095)
    - Interview on Latin American Common Market Affairs, 1963 March 13; Sound, Black and white, 16 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1086)
      Governor Rockefeller interviewed for KRNT-TV in Des Moines, Iowa
    - Episode of Meet the Press, 1963 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1267)
      Episode begins with NBC coverage of the bombing of an African-American church in Birmingham, Alabama. Followed by episode of Meet the Press hosted by Ned Brooks. Includes original commercials. Filmed during presidential campaign.
    - Visit to Colby Junior College, 1963 October 19; Silent, Black and white, 1 minute; 16mm film (Reel AV 1257)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Governor Rockefeller with wife, Happy, visiting Colby Junior College.
    - Pure Waters Conference, 1963 November 12; Sound, Black and white, 3 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1221)
      WRGB footage from the Pure Waters Conference held in the Capitol Building, Albany, after passage of the Pure Waters Bond Issue Prop #1.
    - NAR on Face the Nation, 1963 November 17; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1097)
      Episode filmed during presidential campaign.
    - Nelson Rockefeller: The Man and His Record, 1963; 16mm film; Silent, Black and white (Reel AV 2859)
  - 1964
    - NAR and Staff, 1964; Silent, Black and white, 1 minute; 16mm film (Reel AV 1066)
      Brief clip of Nelson Rockefeller with his staff at West 55th Street office; shot by Wolper Productions for campaign film "Making of the President 1964".
    - 1964 California: San Diego, Kiwanis Club, Silent, Black and white, 50 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1587)
    - Rockefeller's Way, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 5 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1251)
      Campaign spot from 1964 California primary
    - The Extremists, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1155)
      A never-aired 1964 campaign film produced by Nelson Rockefeller And Dave Garroway about the Minutemen, the John Birch Society, and other extremist groups.
      Video transfer available to access: AV 10597
    - The Nelson Rockefeller Story, 1964; Sound, black and white; 16mm film (Reel AV 1754)
    - Gov. Rockefeller Interrupted by a Laughing Baby, 1964 February 28; Sound, Black and white, 20 seconds; 16mm film (Reel AV 75)
      Nelson Rockefeller speech about opposing unilateral negations with Russia interrupted a baby laughing, during New Hampshire primary.
    - NAR on Face the Nation, 1964 March 8; Sound, Black and white, 20 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1081)
      Filmed during presidential campaign.
    - Gov. Rockefeller in New Orleans, 1964 April; Sound, Black and white, 15 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1087)
      Speech on Inter-American affairs.
    - Kup's Show: NAR 1964 Campaign Interview, 1964 May 7; Sound, Black and white, 56 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1941)
      Nelson Rockefeller interview on The Irv Kupcinet Show during presidential campaign. Also features William Rentschler, a Chicago businessman and Barry Goldwater supporter.
    - NAR Address to the Republican National Convention, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 14 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1099)
    - Gov. Rockefeller Speech at Stanford University, 1964 April 1; Sound and silent, Black and white, 11 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1697)
      Speech about the United Nations during California primary.
    - Gov. Rockefeller Speech at UCLA, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 20 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1077)
      Nelson Rockefeller speech outdoors at UCLA, then inside for question/answer session with students during California primary.
    - Gov. Rockefeller in Palm Springs and San Diego, 1964; Silent, Black and white, 50 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1268)
      Campaigning during California primary.
    - 1964 Address to the New York State Legislature, Sound, Black and white, 22 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1076)
      Governor Rockefeller annual address to the state legislature, filmed in Albany, New York.
    - 1964 Oregon Primary, Silent, Color and Black and white, 7 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1235)
      footage of Nelson Rockefeller campaigning throughout Oregon during presidential campaign, with some nonpolitical footage of wildlife, landscapes, and aerial views of the state.
  - 1965
    - NAR on Face the Nation, 1965 July 25; Sound, Black and white, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1089)
    - Governor and Mrs. Nelson Rockefeller at the Orange County, Chenango, and St. Lawrence County Fairs, 1965 August; Silent, Black and white, 27 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1597)
      Nelson Rockefeller with wife at NY county fairs.
    - Governor and Mrs. Nelson Rockefeller at the Camp Drum, Monroe, and Steuben County Fairs, 1965 August; Silent, Black and white, 42 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1596)
      Nelson Rockefeller with wife at public events around the state.
    - Gov Rockefeller and Wife at Fort Schuyler, Bronx, New York, 1965 August 24; Silent, Black and white, 10 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1556)
      Footage of military ship "Empire State IV" arriving at Fort Schuyler in the Bronx; crowds of families waiting to greet sailors. Shot by Hal Posner.
    - Adirondack: Horseback Ride through Forest Preserve, 1965 October 10; Silent, Black and white, 2 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1214)
      Edited footage from UPI Commercial News Service provided to New York State television stations.
    - United Nations Plaza Dedication, 1965 October 25; Silent, Black and white, 1 minute (Reel AV 1546)
      Ceremony and presentation of memorial stairway and flagpole in honor of Dog Hammarskjold, secretary-president of the United Nations, at UN Plaza in New York City.
    - Man in Office, 1965 October 31; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1752)
      Governor Rockefeller interviewed by Joe Michaels on NBC-TV.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller on Issues and Answers, 1965 November 7; Sound, Black and white, 28 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1639)
      III 14.1 Ff 20
    - Gov. Rockefeller Receives Award from Nation Council of Christians and Jews, 1965 November 15; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 16mm film (Reel AV 1216)
      CBS-TV footage of award ceremony at Hilton Hotel in New York City
  - 1966
    - 1966 Campaign Commercials, Sound, Black and white, 23 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1147)
      Sample reel of campaign commercials from 1966 gubernatorial race.
    - The Time is Now, 1966; Sound, Black and white, 20 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1109)
      Political film produced by the Republican National Finance Committee before the 1966 election. Discusses domestic and international issues that have been caused by the Democratic majority in the U.S., with sound bites from Eisenhower, Ford, Nixon, Gov. Rockefeller, and others.
    - Friend of the Rockefeller Team: Campaign Commercials 1, 1966; Sound, Black and white, 22 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1110)
      Compilation of 31 political ads from 1966 campaign, ranging from 10 to 60 seconds each. Topics include: Pure Water Program, state scholarships, the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Medicaid, the narcotics reform laws, education, minimum wage, air pollution, and a message from Jacob Javits.
    - Friend of the Rockefeller Team: Campaign Commercials 2, 1966; Sound, Color, 5 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1114)
      Compilation of 4 campaign commercials produced for the 1966 campaign (?): "4 R's" (education),"Pay Envelope" (jobs), "Consumer Fraud" (consumer protection), "Detective" (criminal intelligence system).
    - 1966 Address to the New York State Legislature, 1966 January 5; Sound, Black and white, 60 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1739)
      Footage of Governor Rockefeller address, filmed by the New York State Department of Commerce
    - The State Vs. the Addict, 1966 March 6; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1075)
      Panel discussion with Nelson Rockefeller, Donald Louria, Wyatt Tee Walker, interviewed by Bill Beutel and Murphy Martin.
    - Opening of Republican State Committee Campaign Headquarters, 1966 June 6; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1220)
      From 1966 campaign, footage of Governor Rockefeller, Governor Malcolm Wilson, Attorney General Louis Lefkowitz at the Hilton Hotel in New York City.
    - Nelson Rockefeller: Formal Announcement of Candidacy, 1966 April 6; 16mm film (Reel AV 1583)
      Nelson Rockefeller announces his intention to run for governor.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      No audio at beginning and ending of film.
    - Labor and the Public Employee, 1966 May 15; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1753)
      Discussion between Nelson Rockefeller, George Taylor, and Mort Dean, shown live on CBS-TV.
    - The 1966 New York Republican State Convention: Governor Rockefeller's Acceptance Speech, 1966 September; 16mm film (Reel AV 1751)
      Nelson Rockefeller acceptance speech at the GOP State Convention, with an introduction from Senator Jacob Javits, broadcast live.
    - Nelson Rockefeller: Election Night Victory Celebration, 1966 November 8; Silent, Black and white, 11 minutes (Reel AV 2875)
      Highlights of Nelson A. Rockefeller victory speech at Hilton Hotel in New York, Footage of Lieutenant Governor Malcolm Wilson, Attorney General Louis Lefkowitz, and State Comptroller Charles Wilson.
  - 1967
    - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller 1967 Inauguration, 1967 January 2; Silent, Color, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1740)
      Inauguration in the Assembly Chamber in Albany, NY. Benediction is given by Dr. Sandy Ray of the Cornerstone Baptist Church in Brooklyn, NY. Note: These are silent cutaways shots filmed by Hal Posner on handheld camera.
    - Annual Message to Legislature, 1967 January 4; Sound, Color, 60 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1862)
      Unedited footage of Nelson Rockefeller annual address in the Assembly Chambers in Albany, New York.
  - 1968
    - Rockefeller - The Presidential Man, 1968; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1765)
      30-minute version of campaign film, with introduction by Lieutenant General James Gavin. Produced by Robert Drew Films.
    - Rockefeller - The Man Who Can, 1968; Sound, Color, 60 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1815)
      One-hour version of campaign film. Produced by Robert Drew Films
      Digitally accessible from 2-inch video transfer: AV 10631
    - Annual Message to Legislature, 1968 January 3; Silent, Color, 24 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1820, Reel AV 1814)
      Unedited footage of Nelson A. Rockefeller annual speech to the New York State Legislature, filmed in the Assembly Room at the Capitol in Albany, New York.
    - Episode of Panorama with Nelson A, Rockefeller, 1968 February; Sound, Black and white, 29 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1743)
      A BBC program from 1968 February which includes some footage used in the 1964 biographical film, "The Nelson Rockefeller Story."
    - Declaration of Non-Candidacy, 1968 March 21; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1085)
      In speech at the Hilton Hotel in New York City, Nelson Rockefeller declares he will not run for the 1968 presidency, in New York.
    - Declaration as Active Candidate, 1968 April 30; Silent, Color, 6 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1569)
      Nelson Rockefeller reverses his previous announcement about the 1968 presidency, in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
    - Rockefeller Statement, 1968 April 30; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1661)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller declares his candidacy, in Albany New YorkY.
    - Gov. Rockefeller at World Affairs Council in Philadelphia, 1968 May 1; Sound, Color, 40 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1089)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller address on foreign policy, "The Building of a Just World Order."
    - 1968 Republican National Convention - Reel 1 and 2, 1968 August 7-8; Sound, Color, 460 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1634)
      Footage of Nelson Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, and others from convention; nomination of Nelson Rockefeller by Gov. Raymond Schafer (PA); thank-you speeches from Nelson Rockefeller and wife; other footage from NBC-TV.
    - Crime Control Week, 1968 December; Sound, Color, 2 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1112)